<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hello World! on Michał Sekuła</title>
    <link>https://sekisekula.github.io/Portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hello World! on Michał Sekuła</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 11:00:59 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sekisekula.github.io/Portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter II: Pierre Gringoire</title>
      <link>https://sekisekula.github.io/Portfolio/projects/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sekisekula.github.io/Portfolio/projects/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Nevertheless, as be harangued them, the satisfaction and admiration unanimously excited by his costume were dissipated by his words; and when he reached that untoward conclusion: “As soon as his illustrious eminence, the cardinal, arrives, we will begin,” his voice was drowned in a thunder of hooting.
“Begin instantly! The mystery! the mystery immediately!” shrieked the people. And above all the voices, that of Johannes de Molendino was audible, piercing the uproar like the fife’s derisive serenade: “Commence instantly!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RealEstateBot: Smart WhatsApp Assistant</title>
      <link>https://sekisekula.github.io/Portfolio/projects/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sekisekula.github.io/Portfolio/projects/project-2/</guid>
      <description>RealEstateBot: Smart WhatsApp Assistant
RealEstateBot is an innovative chatbot designed to assist real estate professionals and their clients, seamlessly integrated with WhatsApp. This smart assistant not only automates the process of answering client queries but also verifies user details in real-time. From providing crucial information like Wi-Fi passwords to sharing property details, it does it all within a few simple messages. RealEstateBot significantly enhances client experience by delivering fast, accurate, and personalized responses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://sekisekula.github.io/Portfolio/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sekisekula.github.io/Portfolio/about/</guid>
      <description>Photo of me :) As a passionate and driven Data Scientist, I specialize in developing data models, dashboards, reports, and performance-driven insights. My expertise in Data Science allows me to leverage advanced analytics on large datasets to uncover patterns and dependencies—skills I’ve honed through hands-on experience. I am adept at presenting complex findings in an intuitive and easily understandable manner, ensuring clear communication with stakeholders.
I am highly motivated to continue learning and advancing my career, with a goal of becoming a Data Science Specialist.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
